is potentially a problem in the future for Republicans if a Democratic president someday
calls the National Guard to a red state over what they see as open rebellion, but is what
amounts to a demonstration that gets rowdy?
I mean, is that not a few years?
Yes, and they're posting pictures of their kids because it's a demonstration, and they
have a sniper on top of a building firing a high-caliber rifle at a nice facility because
it's a demonstration, and they are engaged in a vehicle ramming attacks.
The National Guard isn't being sent to Dallas where that sniper was.
Because the Dallas Police Department and the governor of Texas, well, you walked right
into that one, have responded to every call for assistance and help.
They gave a stand-down order in Chicago, and they gave a stand-down order in Portland.
Do you realize that there's 11,000 federal law enforcement officers in Oregon?
That's larger than the size of the FBI.
Local and state police are resourced to deal with this kind of riotous assembly, but they
have refused.
They're going to be given a stand-down order.
So, we need to use the National Guard and federal troops to fill in that breach.
They've been arresting folks on the ground.
They repeat what you're saying outright.
They repeat what you haven't touched.